<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<testimonials>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
     I took your course in July 2011 and took the exam a month later and passed first time out. I wanted to thank our instructor David Wilf for making the course meaningful and practical. He provided a great experience of knowledge transfer that helped my identify my weaknesses, thus allowing me to focus my efforts on study. Great job.
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Jason Davis, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	19
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
     I passed the PMP exam! Just thought you would want to know. Have a great day.  I know I will!
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Michele Elliott, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	20
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
     Hi Michael! Just wanted to let you know that I passed my PMP exam today! Thanks again for being a great instructor and sharing many stories with us.
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Carla Hala, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	21
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
     Thanks for the training last week! Just to let you know, I passed the exam on Tuesday. Please let me know if you have any questions or concerns, thanks!
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Milla Saaristenperä, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	22
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
     I passed. It's a beautiful thing!  Thanks Keith!
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Dan Lawrence, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	23
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
     I was glad to see the "PASSED" message on the screen yesterday. Thanks to Remy for excellent preparation course, individual study plan and tips for exam. It really helped me very well.
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Bala Subramaniyan, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	24
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
     Yippee!!!!  Just passed the exam! hope you all do the same.
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Nick Raymond, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	25
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
     Praise God!  Thank you so much for helping me pass.
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Ronaldo Montmann, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	26
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
     Thank you Remy.  I passed the exam on Thursday!!
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Dan Derosia, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	27
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
     Hi, Kathleen.  I wanted to let you know that I passed the PMP Certification Exam yesterday in Atlanta. Thanks for your help!
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Raj Birbal, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	28
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
     Hi Marleen. Passed the PMP exam today! Could not have done it without taking the course that you taught in Boston. THANK YOU!
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Paul Hogan, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	29
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
     I wanted to reach out to you to inform you I passed the PMP Exam yesterday. Thanks Joey!
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Leiba Parish, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	30
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
     Hi Michael, I enjoyed your PMP prep class last week and am happy to report that I passed the exam on Friday J Thanks for your help and support!
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Jennifer Johnson, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	31
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
      Not easy, but I got it. Thanks for your help!
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Behrang Abadi, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	0
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
      I passed!
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Matt Hilbrich, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	1
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
      Finally got to take my exam today and passed with flying colors (or at least I like to think so)!  Thanks for all your help!
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Pam Gorky, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	2
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
      I just wanted to drop a note and let everyone know.  I sat for the PMP exam yesterday and passed thanks to Pinnacle 3!  My most sincere thanks to all of you, but particularly to Kathleen for sharing her knowledge and providing excellent training.  I am more than happy to recommend Pinnacle 3 training to anyone looking to prepare for the exam.  Thanks again!
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Chad Browning, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	3
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
      Thanks Keith, I dominated it!!!
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Juliane Mahlmann, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	4
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
      I am on Cloud 9 right now, so happy that I passed the PMP.  I can't thank you enough for your teaching methods, advise and take home materials.  I couldn't have done it without taking your preparation course.

      Thank you again!
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Mary E. Ascolillo, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	5
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
      I successfully passed the PMP exam today. Thanks for your help and guidance.
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Balaji Pattabhiraman, P.M.P.
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	6
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
      I just wanted to follow up and let you know I took the PMP exam today in Denver and passed it. Thanks for all of your help with the classes.
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Bob MacKinnon, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	7
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
      FYI, I took the PMP exam on Saturday (yes, the day after Christmas), and passed.  Thanks for your help.
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Shawn Tovey, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	8
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
      Just wanted to let you know I passed the PMP exam yesterday.  I'd like to thank Keith
      and Pinnacle 3 for your assistance - I couldn't have done it without you.
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Tracy Brooks, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	9
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
      I just wanted to let you know that I passed the PMP exam this morning.  Thanks for your help.  I could not have passed without the class.
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Jeremy Hughes, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	10
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
      Just wanted to let you know I passed the pmp this afternoon...thanks for being a big help at getting me through this...your teaching style was great...and helped tremendously!
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Dawn Sealey, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	11
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
      Thanks!! With the help of your March 2-5 PMP exam prep, I easily passed the PMP certification three weeks later. I will certainly recommend this program to anyone interested.
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Steve Johnson, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	12
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
      Just wanted you to know I passed the PMP exam this morning. Thanks for your help to prepare. I am SO GLAD I passed first try!
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Terri A. Bessom, M.B.A., PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	13
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
      I wanted to take a moment to pass along that I sat for the PMP exam yesterday.  I was able to pass the exam.  Thank you for your help in the prep course.  I would not have passed without that course and what you taught me.  Have a great day.
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Bob Rackham, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	14
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
      I passed!! You'll all do fine.  Mike knows how to get us prepared. Best of luck.  I enjoyed working with you all.
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Bill Needell, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	15
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
      Hi Ms. King! Great news!  I passed :-) The exam was harder than I expected and it was exhausting! Thank you so much for your awesome class and great support. I had a great time learning from you and enjoyed my time with you very much!
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Moe Al-Khazzaz, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	16
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
      The PMP preparation class from Pinnacle 3 is designed from the ground up to drill the key points into you, while also providing some real-world context for reinforcement. I found the approach of using worksheets, diagramming, and flash card creation/reviews to be really helpful. By the end of the 4-day prep, I was confident that I'd do well on the exam. Thanks!
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Andrew K Tsui, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	17
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
  <testimonial>
    <quote>
      Excellent class!  Michael was a great instructor.  I believe everyone felt the class delivered everything expected and then some.
    </quote>
    <reference>
      Tyler Montgomery, PMP
    </reference>
	<sequence>
	18
	</sequence>
  </testimonial>
</testimonials>